ELIZABETE DE PAULA

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- ☐ elizabete.paula@live.com
- linkedin.com/in/elizabete-paula
- github.com/elizaspaula

PROFILE

My passion for technology comes from my experience as a System Analyst. I loved the challenge of facing projects problems and delivering solutions that make people's life easier.

My experience as a System Analyst gives me the ability to see problems from a bird's eye view and helps me design better, more robust solutions.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, SQL, MySQL, Web APIs, ERP, Integrations, Document Object Model (DOM), ITIL V3, Cobit, User Authentication, JIRA

EDUCATION

BRAINSTATION | Web Development

FEB 2022 - APR 2022, VANCOUVER, BC

LIGHTHOUSE LABS | Intro to Web Development

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021, VANCOUVER, BC

VANZOLINI | Diploma, Business Analysis JUL 2015 - NOV 2015, SAO PAULO, BR

FATEC | Associate's degree, Business Management Informatics

JUN 2009 - APR 2011, SAO PAULO, BR

WORK EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Landsure System | Mar 2020 - Aug 2021, Vancouver, BC

- Maintained a 98% success rate on first-call resolutions by delivering excellent customer service using strong interpersonal skills.
- Resolved an average of 30 inquiries daily by using problem-solving skills to troubleshoot customer issues resulting in meeting targets for productivity and quality.

CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER

Carecru | Apr 2019 - Feb 2020, Vancouver, BC

- Created personalized coaching sessions and action plans to successfully ensure each new customer implementation met all requirements and improved customer satisfaction.
- Built trust in the brand by responding efficiently and helpfully to customer needs.

SENIOR SYSTEM ANALYST

Sestini Mercantil | Dec 2015 -Apr 2019, Sao Paulo, BR

- Successfully implemented a new enterprise resource planning system that helped to increase the finance strategy and supply chain performance in the company.
- Cataloged over 10 business processes demonstrating the interaction between data and system using BaBook business analyses methodologies.
- Built and created tests matrix to ensure maximum testing scenarios meet all required specifications.

MID-SENIOR SYSTEM ANALYST

Benner Systems | Feb 2012 - Dec 2015, Sao Paulo, BR

- Responsible for gathering requirements, design of system enhancements, implementation and configuration, testing and production support for various clients in a multi-tenant ERP hosted solution.
- Performed gap analysis interacting with business users to design and implement appropriate solutions for process and system functionality gaps.

PROJECTS

BRAINSTATION CAPSTONE PROJECT

Developer | Mar 2022

 A web app allows users to search for ethical and registered cat breeders in Canada. The app allows the user to filter that by breed and location. Built using React, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS

BENNER ERP IMPLEMENTATION

Sestini Mercantil Dec 2015 - Apr 2019

 Acting as technical deployment consultant in Sestini projects, optimizing business process, validating features and requirements with the development team, and monitoring the development and approval of the communication system between the ERP and integrations.

BENNER ERP IMPLEMENTATION

Benner Systems | Feb 2012 - Dec 2015

• Involved in group projects designed to standardize new procedures with peer groups. Develop and utilize best practices to promote efficient deployments and help customers maximize value.